somethingturquoise.com 2013-10-07

# Privacy Policy » Something Turquoise {ideas for the DIY bride}

Your privacy is very important to us here at SomethingTurquoise.com. In order to protect that privacy you should know that everything that can be done is being done to make your visit as safe and enjoyable as possible. Something Turquoise provides this notice to inform you of how information is collected and or used when you visit this website.

You may visit without revealing any personal information.

Be aware that Something Turquoise does not control what other companies do and you should visit and review the privacy policy of any ‘Linked’ third party or individual not employed by us. We are not responsible for any contract you enter into with anyone beside Something Turquoise.

### What Something Turquoise Collects & Shares

When visiting www.somethingturquoise.com your IP address along with dates and times of access are automatically collected for administrative purposes.  This information is not linked to any personal information.  The only personal information collected is with your approval as when you make a comment (and your email address is required) or when it is needed to provide services or send products to you (physical address/P.O. Box).  By accessing these services you voluntarily provide the necessary information and are thereby consenting to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. Something Turquoise may need to share this information with third parties whose privacy policies agree with its own.   We may also need to disclose this information when:

  * You give express permission for specified purposes
  * We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or other such legal process
  * We need to protect the safety of other users of the website
  * To protect or defend the owners personal rights and/or property
  * Or, if it is found that your actions on the website violate Terms of Use.

### Terms of Use

Your thoughts, opinions, and suggestions are always welcome.  Please, remember, to be respectful! All comments are subject to approval and we reserve the right to delete any comments deemed inappropriate, offensive or spam. If you have a grievance, Something Turquoise is not the proper venue to air such complaints.  All comments should be in keeping with the sites theme. You might not always agree with or like what is shown as inspiration but these are real peoples events and creations and your comments should be respectful. Site users are fully responsible for anything they post in their comments and all posted comments are in the public domain. In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm) all comments posted by children under the age of 13 will be removed. If you would like to endorse or promote a product please email Something Turquoise for information.  Something Turquoise accepts advertising per FTC regulations.  The views and opinions of any guest blogger are not necessarily the same as Something Turquoise.  Information used on Something Turquoise is for educational, informational, and inspirational purposes only and is not contracted advice.  When you click on a third party vendor you are leaving SomethingTurquoise.com and are no longer under its guidelines.

### What 3rd Parties Collect

Some of the advertisements that appear on www.somethingturquoise.com’s web site are delivered to you by national internet advertising and application companies such as Cox Digital Solutions.  This company utilizes certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to our site(s), including information about the banner ads they display, and cookies they place on your computer and your IP address. To opt out of information collection by Cox Digital Solutions, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their most current privacy policy, please visit: http://www.coxdigitalsolutions.com/privacy-policy/consumer-opt-out program  and/or http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.”

### Editorial Policy

Something Turquoise takes every precaution to ensure that copyright laws are adhered to and credits all owners of image or content accordingly. Should you own a photo and wish to have it removed, we reserve the right to request proof of ownership. To request removal contact jen @ somethingturquoise.com. Something Turquoise regularly shares images that we do not hold the copyright to, except where otherwise noted. Each images copyright belongs to the respective photographer credited. Photos used on Something Turquoise are used with the knowledge and permission of the respective photographer or are believed to be readily available in the public domain and used under protection of the US. Copyright Fair Use Act. Something Turquoise accepts paid editorial coverage. These posts will be clearly denoted as such with the words “Sponsored Post” appearing at the end of the post. Editorial content is regularly featured by advertisers and non-advertisers alike. Any photo readily available in the public domain is protected under the fair use act (http://www.copyright.gov/fls/fl102.html).

### Foreign Country User Policy

SomethingTurquoise.com ’s operation is located in the United States of America (US). Any information coming from any other country will be transferred to the US and you are consenting to this transfer, storage and use as described herein.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may at any time, without prior notice, amend this policy. Please review this policy periodically. Should you use SomethingTurquoise.com after the policy has been amended, acceptance of all changes is implied.

### Questions or Suggestions

If you have any questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please contact the owners through the website or email jen [at] somethingturquoise.com .
